gmacfs.com 2016-06-16

# Our Privacy Policy | Ally

## Online Privacy Policy

You take online privacy seriously, and so does the Ally group of companies which includes Ally Financial and Ally Bank. At Ally, we’re committed to protecting the personal information of visitors to our websites.

Our online privacy policy describes the information we collect from and about you during your visit to our websites. It also describes how we use information about you, with whom we share it and how we protect it. This policy applies only to those Ally websites that link directly to this policy.

It's important to know that our websites may contain links to third party sites not controlled by Ally or covered by this online privacy policy. We recommend that you check the privacy statements of other sites you visit before providing any personal information.

Once you become a customer of Ally, and once a year while you remain a customer of Ally, we will provide you with a Privacy Notice describing our privacy practices. It will describe and provide any updates to the collection and sharing of personal information about our customers, as required by law. 

  * How does Ally use the personal information it collects online?

We use personal information collected online for various functions, which may include:

    * processing your request for services, products or information
    * improving our customer service and products
    * servicing your account
    * facilitating your participation in online activities.

For example, we may use the information you provide when you complete an online application for a product or service in order to process and evaluate your application. If you request product information, we may use the information you provide to mail you information you request.

We may also use the information you provide to contact you regarding your account and to process or collect payments. In addition, we may collect and use information for analytic purposes, market research or for marketing purposes, as allowed by law.

  * What personal information does Ally collect online?

We collect personally identifiable information ("PII") about you from the information you provide to us when you visit our websites. The information we collect will depend on the Ally website you visit. This information may include, but is not limited to:

    * Name
    * Address
    * Social Security number in whole or in part
    * Phone numbers (including mobile)
    * Account number
    * Account number at a bank or other financial institution, type of bank account and the name of bank or other financial institution
    * Demand Note number
    * Email address
    * Email referral information
    * Date of birth
    * Current residential information including mortgage or rent payments
    * Employment information
    * Income information

  * Does Ally share the personal information it collects online?

We may share the personal information we collect about you with third parties, such as companies performing services on our behalf to provide the products or services you have requested.

As permitted by law, we may also share information collected about you with companies with whom we have formal agreements to offer you financial products and services.

We may share information about you with our affiliates (other companies in the Ally family) and with nonaffiliates for analysis, market research and marketing purposes as allowed by law.

Finally, we may disclose your personal information as otherwise permitted or required by law.

  * Does Ally use cookies or other online technologies to collect information?

We use a variety of technologies, including cookies, to collect information about your online/mobile activity when you visit our website. Cookies are small text files that a website server stores on your computer or device. They’re typically used to remember your account login preferences, monitor website traffic, provide customer support like live chat and help us better customize our site for your individual preferences.

We may also use Flash® objects (sometimes called "Local Shared Objects") as part of our online authentication to help us recognize your computer when you come back to our site. We do not use Flash objects for any online behavioral advertising purpose.

  * Can I disable or delete cookies?

Yes, you can disable cookies by making the appropriate selection from your browser options to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set. However, if you choose to disable or delete cookies, you may limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our site.

For more information, please view our Online Privacy Policy.

  * Does Ally track my online activity on your websites?

To improve your customer experience, we may use online tracking technologies like cookies to learn more about your online and mobile activities. We track data such as search terms, page visits and link clicks. This helps us provide more relevant online and offline information including, custom content and recommended products and services tailored to your interests.

  * Does Ally use online behavioral advertising (OBA) on third party sites?

There are two ways we use OBA on third party websites and mobile apps that are not affiliated with Ally.

**Interest‐Based Advertising**   
The third parties we contract with may use cookies or other technologies to gather interest-based information to customize the ads you see. Neither the third parties nor Ally collects any personally identifiable information (PII) through these cookies. We may also use aggregate data to display ads or content that may interest you.

Ally has adopted the use of the [AdChoices Icon](http://www.youradchoices.com/) (also known as the Advertising Option Icon) on our interest-based advertising (excluding ads appearing on platforms that do not accept the icon). You can click the AdChoices Icon to learn more and control whether or not you receive this type of advertising from participating companies.

**Device-Based Advertising**   
We also use device information, particularly in mobile advertising, to help deliver our ads and measure ad campaign effectiveness. Ally and the companies we work with won’t collect any personally identifiable information (PII) but may collect your device information when you visit one of our sites or see our ads. Compiling and comparing this information creates a unique ID for individual devices and can be "matched" to the same information on other sites or mobile applications. Some companies we work with are also able to associate related devices into households based on common characteristics, such as IP addresses.

  * How do your websites respond to web browser "Do Not Track" signals?

We do not respond to Web browser "Do Not Track" signals at this time. To prevent Ally or third parties from tracking, you can access your browser settings and disable or delete your cookies.

  * How can I change or update my personal information with Ally?

If you have questions about personal information you provided on an Ally website, select the "Contact Us" link – usually found in the navigation menu – or log into your Ally Auto account and select Account Information to edit your personal information or your Ally Bank account and select My Profile to edit your personal information.

  * What steps does Ally take to protect personal information it collects online?

We restrict access to the personal information obtained from our website to only those employees, agents and contractors who need it to do their jobs. We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to protect your personal information.

Additionally, companies that provide online services on our behalf are required by contract to protect customer information. They are only allowed to use the information they collect for the purpose of providing the services that we have contracted to them.

  * Does Ally collect personal information online about children?

We don't intentionally collect or maintain data about children under 13 unless the personal information is provided by a parent, legal guardian or authorized adult. Our websites are not intended for children under 13.

  * Does Ally make public forums available on its websites?

Public forums are available on our websites, and they may include text, photographs and videos that are accessible to the general public. Unless we tell you otherwise, any information you disclose in these areas may become public information. You should use caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas.

  * Will Ally make changes to this online privacy policy?

This policy is effective January 1, 2016. We reserve the right to alter this policy at our discretion. Any change to this policy will be posted on our websites in a timely manner.

## Social Security Number Privacy Protection Policy

The Ally group of companies  ("Ally") collects Social Security numbers as necessary to support state and federal legal requirements, to provide products or services to you and to meet needs within our Human Resources unit. To support these requirements, we restrict the access to Social Security numbers only to employees, agents, service providers, and government entities that require access to Social Security numbers to meet these purposes. We strive to protect Social Security numbers from unlawful disclosure and keep them confidential by maintaining administrative, technical, and physical safeguards that comply with applicable state and federal regulations.
